Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1902-1991
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1902-1991
1899-1991
RU 261
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(22 microfilm reels)
The microfilmed records consist of undergraduate and graduate student records, class letters, biographical data on alumni, correspondence, transcripts, and necrology files documenting the students from the Classes of 1902-1991, Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies.
Yale University. School of Forestry and Environmental Studies
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 24-F (YRG 24-F), Student records of the Yale School of Forestry.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The microfilmed records consist of undergraduate and graduate student records, class letters, biographical data on alumni, correspondence, transcripts, and necrology files documenting the students from the Classes of 1902-1991, Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Yale University. School of Forestry; Yale University. School of Forestry and Environmental Studies; Yale University -- Students
- Student records (microfilm), circa 1899-1981; Accession 1981-A-060
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057.
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, articles, clippings over the lifetime of students, summer students, and ex-students.
  - 1902-1910 (Reel 1)
  - 1911-1919 (Reel 2)
  - 1920-1928 A-G (Reel 3)
  - 1928 H-W - 1933 Hawes, Evan C. (Reel 4)
  - 1933 Hetzel - 1939 Mish (Reel 5)
  - 1939 Nelson - 1946 Moulds (Reel 6)
  - 1946 Pochan - 1949 Troop (Reel 7)
  - 1949 Turner - 1953 Sutherland (Reel 8)
  - 1953 Swilley - 1958 Makel (Reel 9)
  - 1958 Mitchell - 1962 Keniston (Reel 10)
  - 1962 Kostuvick - 1964 Staniar (Reel 11)
  - 1964 Steber - 1969 Carlson (Reel 12)
  - 1969 Cherington - 1971 Sarigumba (Reel 13)
  - 1971 Scopp - 1973 Wildermann (Reel 14)
  - 1974-1976 (Reel 15)
  - Necrology files-ends with Dean 1929 (Reel 16)
  - Necrology files-Mason 1923-Simmons 1909 (Reel 17)
  - Necrology files-Spelman 1922-McGrath 1955 (Reel 18)
  - Student Transcripts, 1931-1981 (Reel 19)
  - Student Transcripts-Master of Forestry and Special Students, Doctor of Philosophy (1929-1960), Master of Science (1931-1955) and incomplete, 1902-1960 (Reel 20)
- Student transcripts for the Classes of 1981-1990 (microfilm), 1977-1990; Accession 1991-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066.
  - Student transcripts for the Classes of 1981-1990 (microfilm) (Reel 1)
- Student transcripts for the Class of 1991 (microfilm), 1987-1991; Accession 1992-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067.
  - Student transcripts for the Class of 1991 (microfilm) (Reel 1)